// An array that holds all the questions and possible answers, including the corrent answer.
const allQuestionsEasy = [
    {
        question: 'Which club has won the most Champions League titles?',
        answers: ['AC Milan', 'Marseille', 'Real Madrid', 'Liverpool', 2],
    },
    {
        question: 'Who won the English Premier League in 2022/23?',
        answers: ['Man City', 'Arsenal', 'Man Utd', 'Newcastle', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which team palys at Stamford Bridge?',
        answers: ['West Ham', 'Fulham', 'Crystal Palace', 'Chelsea', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who was the top goal scorer in the English Premier League in 2022/23?',
        answers: ['Mo Salah', 'Harry Kane', 'Ivan Toney', 'Erling Haaland', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the manager of Liverpool FC?',
        answers: ['Mikel Arteta', 'Jürgen Klopp', 'Eddie Howe', 'Erik ten Hag', 1]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who owens Wrexham FC?',
        answers: ['Ryan Reynolds & Rob McElhenney)', 'Brad Pitt', 'Tom Cruise', 'Tom Hanks', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who plays at the Queen Elizabeth Stadium?',
        answers: ['Norwich', 'Celtic', 'West Ham', 'Leeds', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the capital of Ireland?',
        answers: ['Cork', 'Galway', 'Waterford', 'Dublin', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'How many clubs played in the first Premier League?',
        answers: ['22', '20', '24', '18', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the captain of Liverpool FC?',
        answers: ['Mo Salah', 'Jordan Henderson', 'Virgil Van Djik', 'Nunez', 1]
    }
];

const allQuestionsMedium = [
    {
        question: 'For what club did Paulo Di Canio play when he pushed referee Paul Alcock?',
        answers: ['West Ham', 'Everton', 'Sheffield Wednesday', 'Sheffield United', 2],
    },
    {
        question: 'Which manager was in charge at Manchester City when they won their first Premier League title?',
        answers: ['Mark Hughes', 'Pep Guardiola', 'Roberto Mancini', 'Manuel Pellegrini', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'Andriy Shevchenko is from which nation?',
        answers: ['Ukraine', 'Hungary', 'Denmark', 'Russia', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'What Was Cristiano Ronaldos First Club?',
        answers: ['Benfica', 'Porto', 'Sporting Lisbon', 'Man Utd', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who Is The All-Time Top Scorer In La Liga?',
        answers: ['Luis Figo', 'Ronaldo', 'Owen', 'Messi', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who Won The World Cup In 1998?',
        answers: ['France', 'Brazil', 'Germany', 'Italy', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Country Has Won The World Cup The Most Times?',
        answers: ['Germany', 'Brazil', 'Spain', 'Ireland', 1]
    },
    {
        question: 'What Is The German Soccer League Called?',
        answers: ['The Blitzliga', 'The Volksliga', 'The Bundesliga', 'The Reichsliga', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'What year did the Premier League start?',
        answers: ['1991', '1992', '1993', '1994', 1]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the Premier League’s all-time leading goal scorer?',
        answers: ['Robbie Fowler', 'Andy Cole', 'Alan Shearer', 'Harry Kane', 2]
    }
];

const allQuestionsHard = [
    {
        question: 'Which two non-English clubs have played in the Premier League?',
        answers: ['Swansea & Cardiff', 'Celtic & Rangers', 'Halifax & Wrexham', 'Liverpool & Everton', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who scored the first-ever Premier League goal?',
        answers: ['Alan Shearer', 'Ian Rush', 'Brian Deane', 'Les Ferdinand', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'In what season did Arsenals Invincibles go the whole season unbeaten?',
        answers: ['2001/02', '2002/03', '2003/04', '2004/05', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who scored the first Premier League hat-trick?',
        answers: ['Stan Colymore', 'Robbie Keane', 'Kevin Philips', 'Eric Cantona', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who are the only team to have received a gold version of the Premier League trophy??',
        answers: ['Arsenal', 'Liverpool', 'Leicster', 'Chelsea', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who has managed Reading, Swansea and Liverpool?',
        answers: ['Roy Hodgson', 'Brendan Rodgers', 'Glen Hoddle', 'Gerry Francis', 1]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who was the first English manager to win the Premier League Manager of the Year award?',
        answers: ['Harry Redknapp', 'Howard Wilkinson', 'Howard Kendall', 'Sam Allardyce', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'In what season did Roman Abramovich take over Chelsea?',
        answers: ['Montego Bay', 'Port Antonio', 'Santa Cruz', 'Kingston', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'The winners of the UEFA Champions League and the UEFA Europe League compete for which sporting trophy?',
        answers: ['FA Cup', 'World Clup Cup', 'UEFA Super Cup', 'FAI Cup', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which two teams share the Stadio Giuseppe Meazza?',
        answers: ['Ajax & Rotterdam', 'Celtic & Rangers', 'AC & Inter Milan', 'Real Madrid & Barcelona', 2]
    }
];